

LÊ TUẤN ANH

BACKEND DEVELOPER

ABOUT ME

Careful and meticulous is a backend developer with extensive experience solving problems clearly and accurately. With 5 years of experience working with Java, I have confidence in understanding the characteristics and elegance of this language. Along with an open mind to learn and not afraid to change I am seeking a position as a backend developer to continue career growth and self-improvement.

SKILLS

- Java, Javascript, Php
- Spring boot, Laravel, Nestjs
- Mysql, Postgresql, MongoDb
- Git, Docker, CI/CD, Vps

CONTACT

+84 326 255 172

□ anhlee99.work@gmail.com

💡 Hồ Chí Minh, Việt Nam

WORK EXPERIENCE

JOINT STOCK COMPANY SHACY | 07/2022 - 07/2023

Backend developer

Tasks:

- Building the pharmacy management software system GDP and GPP.
- Directly design and manage the database.
- Handle API and unit test.
- Integrated national pharmacy system.
- Integrated Viettel e-invoice.
- Troubleshooting from the users.
- Contribute ideas to build features.
- Make plans for database migration and deploy products between environments.

IPI TECHNOLOGY SOLUTIONS COMPANY | 11/2020 - 07/2022

Backend developer

Tasks:

- Build microservice system with more than 15 services on spring boot framework.
- Design parttern, structure modules
- Have experience working with jpa, hibernate, spring-security, apache-shiro, hazelcast, redis, redis-queue...
- Work with muti-database system, replication master-slave.
- Work with elasticsearch system.
- Processing integration with partner via API and FTP.
- Handle API for business logic.
- Control database migration and deploy production.
- Contribute ideas to build features for the system.

FREELANCE PROJECT- DRIVER BOOKING APPLICATION | 02/2023 - 07/2023

Leader Backend developer

Tasks:

- Work with spring boot websocket, muti-thread, session
- Ability to wotk under pressure and work independently.
- Assign tasks and ensure work progress.
- Join the discussion and comment on the feature.
- Control database migration and deploy production.

LANGUAGES

Vietnamese: Native English: Intermediate

EDUCATION

2017-2020 | HCM

Mobile developer

FPT Polytechnic College